[{"answer": "Only with you.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "Why have you finally succumbed to me?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "No, actually, I watched your show since day one and I -- you know, have been admiring it.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "What changed your mind?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Now they want me to ask, how many times have you been properly in love?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "Is it to you?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well, the most recent and the most -- you know, the one I'd like to talk about.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Who with?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "Someone when I was much younger.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Who would the third be?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "The first time your heart really breaks.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "You know that you have one relationship, I think, in your life that's kind of crazy and out of control a little bit that usually doesn't last very long but it takes you into the deep water, into the rough waves, right?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Well.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "You remember it?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "I was always the heart -- the first one, I got my heartbroken badly.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "And who broke whose heart?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "I think, first of all, it opened me up.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "How did it change you emotionally?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Totally.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "But isn't the reality is, when you scale those dizzy height a lot of fun, though, a lot of it is, it can be a quite lonely existence, can it?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "Present company excepted, have you ever been in love with a man?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "His name is Mike, and I've lived with him for about two years.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "Who?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "Well, about the societal approval that you got to have just by virtue of the fact that it was a heterosexual relationship.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "About convention, conventional relationships?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Not for me, I don't think.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Do you feel defensive more than you would normally?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Yes, it's interesting to me that they're not.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "And the three top ones are no longer in the race, right?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "You know, it's a sad lot of contenders.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "What do you make of the GOP race generally?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Why do you feel there's still this fear of being open about sexuality in modern America?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "I don't.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "Do you think mythology builds up about certainly celebrities?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "Well, I think that any new cable start-up takes about five to 10 years to really hit.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "What's your overview now you've been in there a few months?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "I feel like she's the smarter, prettier, older sister that you want to be like.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "But when you two are together, these titans of American television, fire brands in many ways, trailblazers, what's the relationship like between you?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "She has a reach that is undeniable.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "A lot.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "Are you enjoying it?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "Let's turn to your family.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "They're good.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "How are they all?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "And how about when you threaten to kill yourself?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "Do you like Twitter?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Have I?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "I was expecting mayhem.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "What were you expecting?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "I've always thought that in different circumstances, you and I could be quite a hot couple.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "'DONNELL: You think?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Sixteen pounds.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "How much weight have you lost?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "Yes, it's a stone.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Is that a stone?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "November 6th was the day I --", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "In what space of time?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "'DONNELL: You know, working out and eating healthy.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "Two months, 16 pounds?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "You're very obedient then.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "No, I am always sort of obedient in a relationship.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Have you learned to be obedient in a relationship?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "I really do follow orders.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "We met at a Starbucks actually.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "You met in a restaurant?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Million years.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "She's very attractive.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Have you seen her?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "We had talked about it, you know, getting married, but I actually bought the ring and asked the question.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Who proposed to who?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "Well, it was freaking, but you get the point.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "It was her exact word?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "I think it's worked out better because I'm a public figure and they didn't have to sort of tell their friends, or come out at school, everyone sort of just knew.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "Do any of them have any problems with you being gay that you picked up on or has it all worked out in a better way you could ever have imagined?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "It's humiliating and it was probably the most difficult thing that I ever went through in my adult life.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Wasn't it?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "When she said -- when she said that.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "What was the moment for you when you realized it was irretrievable, that you were definitely going to have to split up?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Really well.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "How do you get along with Kelly now?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "I probably would invite her.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Did you invite her to your wedding?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "'DONNELL: She was the president of the PTA.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "What do you remember about your mother?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "What do you think she would have made of how you have grown up?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "Always.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "When you see people who have very close relationships with their mothers, do you feel like you've had this huge void in your life?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "So I would look in the mirror and I would be like, wow.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "What must that have felt like for her?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "So she was aware.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "Can you still cook it?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "Brings back too many painful memories?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "It is sad.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "That's sad, isn't it?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "You know, not very well.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "How did your father deal with it in reality?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "In some ways, I do.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "Now that you've had four kids yourself, have you been able to look back on him in a more favorable light, given the enormity of what was suddenly thrust upon him?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "I have.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "Have you reached that place?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "I have.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "Have you forgiven him, in your mind?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "Shocked.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 763, "question": "Are you surprised they invited him back?", "qSentId": 762}, {"answer": "He's done me a lot of favors.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 783, "question": "You do?", "qSentId": 782}, {"answer": "Say something nice.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 809, "question": "He does?", "qSentId": 808}, {"answer": "I feel like Kofi Annan.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 819, "question": "Is there a surprise guest?", "qSentId": 818}, {"answer": "No, I wasn't given one.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 840, "question": "Yes, a confirmation?", "qSentId": 839}, {"answer": "I'm happy I did it for two reasons.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 856, "question": "How do you feel about being involved in one of the really appalling films ever made?", "qSentId": 855}, {"answer": "Who is great.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 859, "question": "How do you go wrong with that?", "qSentId": 858}, {"answer": "Which is if I could let you relive --", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 883, "question": "Which is?", "qSentId": 882}, {"answer": "It would be this interview, Piers.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 886, "question": "What would it be?", "qSentId": 885}, {"answer": "Admit.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 891, "question": "I have heard you ask that question a million times before?", "qSentId": 890}, {"answer": "I remember on time we were driving home from Rainbow Ranch, which is where she would take my nana and herself to get dresses that were on sale.", "docId": "120117pmt", "aSentId": 897, "question": "Can you remember a particular moment?", "qSentId": 896}]